Guide to the Records of John Brademas Speeches 1965-1991 RG 3.0.10 RG 3.0.10
New York University Archives
- Series I
  - LPB 1990-91 Budget, Washington Square, NYU, (JB memo to NYU Community), Mar 29, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 122)
  - "Salute To Benefactors of NYU Luncheon", Apr 18, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 123)
  - Laudatio of Ailton Krenak, Apr 5, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 124)
  - CASH Luncheon, Apr 12, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 125)
  - JB on Reading, Apr 12, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 126)
  - Senate Report, Apr 12, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 127)
  - Urban Research Center Lunch, Apr 17, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 128)
  - Medical Center Board of Trustees, Apr 17, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 129)
  - Reception at Metropolitan Club, Apr 17, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 130)
  - Salute to Benefactors of NYU Luncheon, Regency Hotel, (Remarks), Apr 18, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 131)
  - Olive Branch Awards Luncheon, Apr 20, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 042254717
  - African Forum on the Economies of Southern Africa, Apr 20, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Founders Day Honors Convocation, Apr 22, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Washington Square Park "Spruce Up", Apr 24, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - NYU Creative Writing Program Benefit, Apr 25, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Sotirhos Luncheon, Apr 25, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - 25 Year Service Awards, Apr 26, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Annual Survey of American Law Tribute, Apr 26, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - League of Woman Voters in the City of NY, Hotel Pierre, (Remarks), Apr 26, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Young Audiences 20th Annual National Conference Lunch, Apr 27, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - African-American and Latino Awards Ceremony, Apr 27, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Brief Statement on 25th Anniversary of Older American Act, May 1, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Quote for NYU Business Magazine, May 1, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Article for the Chronicle of Higher Education, May 1, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Informational Chat with President Endara of Panama, May 2, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Initiation, May 2, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - 25th Anniversary of the Inaguration of Lyndon Baines Johnson, May 3, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Aspen Institute Board Meeting, May 5, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Convocation for Fritz John of Courant, May 9, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Alumni Council Award Dinner, May 9, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - NYU Community Fund-Check Presentation, May 9, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Urban Research Center Conference, May 10, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Endorsing Tim Roemer for Congress, May 11, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - 19th Annual Michiana Prayer Breakfast, May 11, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Luncheon to Honor Prof. Angelos Th. Angelopoulus, May 14, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Board of Trustees, May 14, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - SEHNAP Valedictory Ceremony, May 14, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Friends of Wagner School Dinner, May 15, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Dinner for NFL Commissioner Paul Tagliabue, May 15, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - IFA Board Meeting, May 16, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Trustees Pre-Commencement Dinner, May 16, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Medical School Last Day Exercises, May 17, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Honorary Degree Citations, May 17, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - 158th Annual Commencement Exercises, (Remarks), May 17, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Albert Gallatin Medalist, May 17, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Alumni Commecement Breakfast, May 17, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Cyprus-American Association, May 28, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Groundbreaking for Biomolecular Bldg. at Med. Ctr, Jun 5, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Creative Arts Team 15th Anniversary Celebration, Jun 4, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Dinner celebrating Med. Ctr. Groundbreaking, Jun 5, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Independent Commission, 1st Meeting, Jun 7, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - College of Dentistry Graduation Ceremony, Jun 12, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - 21st Century Club Inagural Dinner, Jun 12, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Reception for La Maison Francaise Advisory Board, Jun 13, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - 1990 C. Walter Nichols Award, Jun 13, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Message to International Assoc. of Permanent Representatives to U.N., Jun 13, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Values/Resources, Jun 18, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Depauw University Speech, Greencastle, Indiana, ("Global Responsibilities and National Interests), Jun 18, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Groundbreaking Ceremony and Reception for Stern, Jun 20, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Management Education Ctr., undated (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Independent Commission, 2nd Meeting, Jun 25, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - 30th- Biennial Clergy-Laity Congress Opening Luncheon, Washington D.C., (Remarks), Jul 9, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - Grand Banquet Honoring His All Holiness, Patriarch Dimitrios, Waldorf-Astoria Hotel, (Remarks), Jul 15, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Letter to Koren Student Association, Jul 18, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - Open Mind Interview, Jul 29, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 55)
  - Graduation Ceremony of Metro's Center's Upward Bound, Aug 10, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 56)
  - Interview with Crain's Business, Aug 10, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 57)
  - Reception for Harvey Stedman, Sep 5, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 58)
  - Dedication William R. Salomon House, Sep 17, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 59)
  - Board of Trustees/ Exec. Committee Meeting, Sep 17, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 60)
  - Presentation of Keogh Awards Alumni Federation Dinner, Sep 18, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 61)
  - Reception at the Greek Cousul General, Sep 18, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 62)
  - Regency Breakfast Meeting of Exec. Development Committee, Sep 18, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 63)
  - Sir Richard Southwood Penthouse Dinner, Penthouse, (Talking Points), Sep 20, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 64)
  - Luncheon for the Naming of John J. Creedon House, Sep 24, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 65)
  - Announcement of Sanwa Bank Endowment, Sep 26, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 66)
  - Penthouse Dinner in Honor of Sheldon Solow and IFA, Sep 26, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 67)
  - Dr. Ivan L. Bennett Jr. Memorial Service, Farkas Auditorium, (Remarks), Sep 27, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 68)
  - Women's Campaign Fund Dinner, Sep 27, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 69)
  - Convocation for Toshiki Kaifu, Loeb, (Remarks), Sep 28, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 70)
  - Mtg w/ Wagner School Visit Committee, Sep 28, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 71)
  - Welcome for President Chamorros of Nicaragua, Oct 1, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 72)
  - Convocation for Carlos Salinas, Loeb, (Remarks), Oct 1, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 73)
  - Letter to Representative Augustus Hawkins, Oct 1, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 74)
  - University Senate, Oct 4, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 75)
  - Testimony on Archives, Oct 4, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 76)
  - The Open Mind, Oct 6, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 77)
  - Tim Roemer Campaign Remarks, Oct 6, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 78)
  - Consecration of Church of St. Andrew, South Bend, Indiana, (Remarks), Oct 6, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 79)
  - NY State Assoc. of Foreign Language Teachers, Kiamesha Lake, New York, (Keynote Speech), Oct 7, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 80)
  - Humanities Council Symposium, Oct 10, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 81)
  - Humanities Council Symposium Dinner, Oct 10, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 82)
  - Dinner for Preston Robert Tisch, Oct 11, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 83)
  - Harvard Class of '49 Dinner & Panel, Harvard Club, (Remarks), Oct 12, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 84)
  - Board of Trustees, Oct 12, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 85)
  - Conference on Fiscal Reform in NY State, Oct 16, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 86)
  - Medical Ctr. Board of Trustees, Oct 16, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 87)
  - Ahmet Ertegun Dinner, Penthouse, (Talking Points), Oct 16, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 88)
  - Interfaith Forum of NY State Religious Leaders, Rye, New York, Oct 17, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 89)
  - Alumni Council Mtg., Oct 17, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 90)
  - Dedication of Nordoff Robbins Music Therapy Clinic, (Remarks), Oct 18, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 91)
  - Interview on Comprehensive Child Development Bill of 1971, Oct 19, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 92)
  - Burger King Honors Excellence in Education Symposium, Oct 23, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 93)
  - Aspen Institute Board Meeting, Oct 30, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 94)
  - Ltr. To Prof. Sam Proctor of University of FL, Nov 1, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 95)
  - Reflections on Education, Nov 1, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 96)
  - Milton Petrle Lecture & Dinner, Nov 1, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 97)
  - Op-Ed Term Limits, Nov 2, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 98)
  - NY Alliance 1990 Teachers Award Luncheon, Nov 2, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 99)
  - Luncheon to Inagurate Health & Policy Mgmt. Chair, Nov 6, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 100)
  - New York Magazine Article, Nov 6, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 101)
  - IFA Board of Trustees, Nov 7, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 102)
  - 4th Annual All Univ. Dinner Dance, Nov 7, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 103)
  - University Senate, Nov 8, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 104)
  - Chet Huntley Memorial lecture and dinner, Tishman Auditorium/Presidents Conference Room, (Remarks), Nov 8, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 105)
  - SEHNAP "American College" Course, Nov 12, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 106)
  - Dedication of Casa Italiana, Nov 12, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 107)
  - Trustee Scholars Reception, Nov 12, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 108)
  - Conference on Jimmy Carter, Hofstra, (Jimmy Carter: Keeping Faith), Nov 14, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 109)
  - ADL Dinner Honoring David Laventhol, Nov 14, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 110)
  - American Assoc. of University Students, Vista Hotel, (Remarks), Nov 15, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 111)
  - Luncheon Honoring Members of the Board of the Alexander S. Onassis Public Benefit Foundation, Penthouse, (Talking Points), Nov 16, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 112)
  - Presentation of the Alexander S. Onassis Center Gold Medal for Excellence in Hellenic Studies to Professor Robert Browning, Tishman Auditorium, (Remarks), Nov 16, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 113)
  - Luncheon Honoring Members of the Union of Greek Shipowners and Conference Participants, Bobst Library, (Talking Points), Nov 17, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 114)
  - NYU Conference on "The Greeks & The Sea", Nov 16, 1990-11/18/1990 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 042254725
  - Residencia de Estudiantes, Madrid, Spain ("Education, Culture and Philanthropy: New Challenges for the New Europe"), Nov 27, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - 50th Anniversary of Federico Garcia's Poet in New York, Dec 3, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Conversation w/ Alexander M. Yakolev, Dec 4, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Bobst Awards in Arts and Letters, Dec 4, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - "Future of the Law School Dinner", Dec 6, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - University Senate, Dec 6, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Carter-Menil Awards, Dec 10, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Board of Trustees, Dec 10, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Medical Center Board of Trustees, Dec 11, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Council Luncheon, Dec 13, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - King Juan Carlos I Professor Lecture, Dec 13, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - USA Today Op-Ed, Dec 23, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - JG American Oxonian Article, ("The Independent Commission: A Commentary"), Jan 4, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - KF Tribute to Dean Robert B. McKay, Century Club, (Article for NYU Law Review), Jan 15, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - KF NY School for the Deaf, Manufacturers Hanover, (JB Remarks & Awardee of 1st Annual Founder Day Award), Jan 15, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - LPB Greek Archdiocese Taping on Hellenic Culture, E. 79th St., (JB Two-Minute Script), Jan 16, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - LPB Introduction of LJO at Alumni Council, NYU, (JB Intro), Jan 16, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - LPB International Rescue Committee Freedom Award Luncheon, New York City, (JB Remarks Honorees: Fang Lizhi Li Shuxian), Jan 24, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - JG Conference on "The National Library in the Life of the Nation" (NOT DELIVERED), Moscow, U.S.S.R,.("Libraries in a Democratic Society"), Jan 28, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - LPB Introduction of Michel Fribourg, La Maison Francaise, (JB Intro), Jan 29, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - DF Italian Trade Commission Reception, Casa Italiana, (JB Talking Points), Jan 31, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - KF IFA Board Meeting, 1 E. 78th St., (JB Report), Feb 6, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - KF International Congress on Trade Cooperation and Investment Opportunities in Czechoslovakia (NOT DELIVERED), Prague, Czech. ,(JB Speech), Feb 7, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - KF University Senate, Bobst-Snow, (JB Report/JLO Talking Points), Feb 14, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - DF Luncheon for Fyodor Burlatsky, Bobst-Conf. Rm, (JB Speech), Feb 14, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - JG AAAS William D. Carey Lecture, Washington, DC, ("American Science in the 21st Century: Prospects & Problems"), Feb 18, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - JG Athenagoras Human Rights Award, Waldorf-Astoria, (JB Tribute Remarks Honoring Award Recipient Andrew Athens), Feb 23, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - KF SEED Speech, Washington, DC, ("Economies in Transition: Management Training & Market Economics Education in Central & Eastern Europe"), Feb 26, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - DF Metro Center Torch of Learning Award, Waldorf-Astoria, (JB Remarks Honoring Award Recipient Lew Rudin), Feb 27, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - DF Gallatin Publishing Program Dinner, Penthouse, (JB Remarks Honoring Alberto Vitale & Robert Jachino), Feb 27, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - LPB Book Review for The Review of Politics, ("The American Speakership: The Office in Historical Perspective"), Feb 27, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - DF Sunday at the Square, Bobst-Atrium, (JB Remarks), Mar 3, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - KF Medical Center Board of Trustees, Med. Sci. Bldg., (JB Report), Mar 5, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - DF United Way/NYU Community Fund, Bobst-Conf. Rm., (JB Brief Remarks), Mar 6, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - DF Luncheon for Sir John Pope-Hennessy, Penthouse, (JB Remarks), Mar 6, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - JB The French-American Conference, Washington, DC, ("America's Unfinished Agenda: The Relationship of Domestic Factors to Foreign Politics"), Mar 8, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - KF Naming of the Abe Burrows Theater, TSOA, (JB Remarks), Mar 14, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - DF National Book Critics Circle Awards, Vanderbilt-Tishman, (JB Remarks), Mar 14, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - DF Sixth Annual Federation Finance Forum, Vanderbilt-Tishman, (JB Welcome), Mar 16, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - KF Board of Trustees, Bobst-Conf. Rm, (JB Report), Mar 18, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - JG Fourth Annual Nancy Hanks Lecture, Washington, D.C., (JB Lecture on Arts & Public Policy), Mar 20, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - DF Metro International Fulbright Awards Dinner, United Nations, (JB Present Award to Alberto Vitale), Mar 21, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - KF University Senate, Bobst-Snow, (JB Report), Mar 21, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - KF Faculty Council Luncheon, Bobst-Conf. Rm., (JB Report), Mar 28, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - DF American Academy of Art & Science, Bobst-Conf. Rm., (JB Remarks/Speaker: Toni Morrison), Apr 2, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - JB Harvard Overseers' Farewell Dinner, Boston, MA, (JB Remarks Honoring Derek Bok), Apr 6, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - DF Luncheon for Elite African Women Conference, D'Agostino Hall, (JB Statement), Apr 9, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - LPB Testimony Before Ways & Means Committee, Washington, DC, (JB Testimony on Employee Educational Assistance), Apr 9, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - DF SEHNAP Alumni Council Awards Dinner, Bobst-Snow, (JB Receives "Torch of Excellence" Award), Apr 10, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - KF University Senate, Bobst-Snow, (JB Report), Apr 11, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - JG Annual Convention of the National School Boards Association, San Francisco, CA, (JB Lecture on Education), Apr 13, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - JG American Oxonian Article, (JB Article on "The Independent Commission: A Commentary"), Apr 15, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - LPB Sheldown Solow Remarks - IFA Luncheon, IFA, (Solow Remarks), Apr 16, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 54)
  - LPB Laudatio of Jimmy Carter Onassis Prize for Man & Society--Aristotelis 1991, Athens, Greece, (JB Remarks Award Honoree: Jimmy Carter), Apr 18, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 55)
  - KF C.A.S.H. Luncheon, Bobst-Conf. Rm,.(JB Talking Points), Apr 21, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 56)
  - KF Founder's Day Honors Convocation, Coles, (JB Remarks), Apr 21, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 57)
  - DF Lecture of George Steiner, Churchill College, Bobst-Conf. Rm., (JB Intro at Lecture/Remarks at Dinner), Apr 22, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 58)
  - KF Kenneth Holland Lecture, U.N. Plaza, ("Strengthening Education & Domestic Policies in Support ofEnlightened United States Leadership Abroad"), Apr 23, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 042254733
  - DF 25-Year Service Awards, Bobst-Snow, (JB Brief Remarks), Apr 24, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - KF Kean College Masters Candidates Convocation, Union, NJ, ("Higher Education & Adult Learners: Directions for the 90's", Apr 24, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - DF Unveiling of Wagner Memorabilia, 4 Wash. Sq. No., (JB Brief Remarks), Apr 24, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - LPB Secretary Lamar Alexander & Chairman William Ford Dinner, Washington, DC, (JB Remarks), Apr 25, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - JG Oregon Council for the Humanities 20th Anniversary Celebration, Portland, OR, (JB Address), Apr 27, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - LPB Kriser Family Dinner, 4 East 60th St,. (JB Brief Remarks), Apr 30, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - DF NYU Community Fund, Bobst-Conf. Rm., (JB Check Presentation), May 1, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - KF University Senate, Bobst-Snow, (JB Report), May 2, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - LPB-MBT Representative Thomas J. Downey Press Conference, Dowling College, (LJO Remarks on Higher Education), May 3, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - LPB Reception for Visiting High School Counselors, Bobst-Conf. Rm,. (JB Talking Points), May 6, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - DF Caring Community Breakfast Meeting, Bobst-Conf. Rm., (JB Talking Points), May 8, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - DF Alumni Council Dinner, Bobst-Snow, (JB Script & Remarks Awards to: Dr. Catherine Cowell, Mr. George Wolfe, Dr. Carl P. Carlucci, Mr. Walter F. Loeb, Dr. Racquel Z. LeGeros, Dr. Henry Kaufman), May 8, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - JG Associates of the Yale Medical Library Annual Meeting, Yale Univ., ("Higher Education in the Nineties: Prospects & Problems"), May 9, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - KF Board of Trustees, Bobst-Conf. Rm., (JB Report), May 13, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - KF Benefit Gala for the America-Italy Society; Danti Aligheri Awards, 122 E. 58th St., (JB Remarks & Presents Awards to Baroness Zerilli-Mariomo), May 14, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - KF IFA Board of Trustees, 1 E. 78th St, (JB Report), May 15, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - LPB Trustees' Pre-Commencement Dinner, Bobst-Snow, (JB & Larry Tisch Remarks), May 15, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - LPB Alumni Commencement Breakfast, Bobst, (JB Remarks), May 16, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - LPB Albert Gallatin Medalist, (Thomas S. Murphy), May 16, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - All Honorary Degree Citations, (Honorees: Stella Adler, Joan Ganz Cooney, Gianluigi Colalucci, Judith Ann Jamison, Victor Frederick, Weisskopf,), May 16, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - LPB JG 159th Commencement Exercises, Wash. Sq. Park, (Commencement Scripts JB & Larry Tisch), May 16, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - KF Medical School Last Day Exercises, Hotel Pierre, (JB Remarks & Intro Lt. Gov. Lundine), May 16, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - KF Pancyprian Association Freedom Award, Hotel Pierre, (JB Remarks & Award Presentation to George Paraskevaides), May 18, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - JG American Association of Museums 86th Annual Meeting, Denver, CO, (JB Keynote Address), May 20, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - LPB Department of Dermatology Dinner, The Water Club, (JB Remarks), May 21, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - KF President's Council Reception, Bobst-Conf. Rm., (JB Remarks), May 21, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - DF 125th Anniversary of College of Dentistry, Penthouse, (JB Remarks), May 22, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - JG University of Thessaloniki Special Lecture, Thessaloniki, Greece ("Key to the 21st Century:Educated Men & Women"), May 30, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - LPB Wolfson College Symposium on "Higher Education: Towards the 21st Century", Oxford, England, ("Higher Education: The Global Perspective"), Jun 7, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - KF Intro of President-Elect of the Russian Federation, Vanderbilt-Tishman, (JB Introduction of Boris Yeltsin), Jun 21, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - LPB U.S. House of Representatives' Committee on Education & Labor Hearing, D'Agostino Hall, (JB Statement/Oral Testimony on the on the Higher Education Act), Jun 24, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - JG NSFRE Award for Achievement in Philanthropy, NY Hilton, (JB Honoree/Brief Remarks), Jun 28, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - JB Message to School of Law, Jul 1, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - KF International Conference on the Environment & University of Barcelona, Barcelona, Spain, ("Education & The Environmental Crisis"), Jul 9, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 35)